"We've got 3 minutes till it blows. We won't make it!"
反應爐3分鐘後就要爆炸
"You've got to get out of here! Save yourself!"
我們逃不掉了 你得趕快逃命
"I won't leave you."
不行，我不會扔下你
"Don't worry about me. I'm a robot. I'm just a machine!"
別管我 我是機器人，我只是一台機器
-"No,you're not. Not to me." -Oh,my God.
對我來說不是 天哪
-What? -I am extremely talented.
怎樣？ 我太有才華了
-Yeah. You're great. -Yeah.
你確很棒
-Okay,let's take it from.. -No,I mean, I was really acting my ass off.
好，我們從… 不是，我真的超會演的
I thought I was pretty good,too.
我覺得我也很不錯
Yeah,you're solid. You're just no me.
你是很不錯，只不過不是我
You know what? I think that's enough for now.
我看就先這樣
I don't want to be over-rehearsed.
我不想排練過頭
Fine. I'll do it without you!
沒關係，我自己演
I don't need you or anybody else!
我不需要你或任何人
I'm gonna make it on my own!
我會靠我自己成功
You'll see! You'll all see!
等著瞧，都給我等著瞧
The One With Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
本集播出：「試鏡風波」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
So what are you auditioning for?
你要去試什麼鏡？
It's a new TV show.
是一部新影集
I'm up for the part of Mac, Machiavelli, or "Mac"!
我的角色叫麥克麥可維利 也叫麥克
I'm a detective and I solve crimes with my robot partner.
我是個偵探 和我的機器人拍檔 一起打擊犯罪
He's a computerized humanoid...
他是人性化電腦
electronically enhanced secret enforcer.
電子秘密殺手
Or "C.H.E.E.S.E."
簡稱吉事
-So Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.? -That's the title!
麥克與吉事 那就是劇名
They lucked out that the initials spell "cheese."
幸好縮寫剛好是吉事
That is lucky.
真是幸好
So Joey,if you get this, you're gonna be,like...
要是你拿到這個角色
the star of your own TV show.
就有你自己的影集了
I mean,you'll be like the "Big Cheese" or the "Big Mac." Hey, you love those!
你就會被稱為大吉事（漢堡） 或是大麥克（麥香堡） 都是你的最愛
Don't get your hopes up. It probably won't happen.
別抱太大期望，應該沒那麼好
Why would you say that?
你為什麼要這麼說？
Well,I mean, come on, guys. My own TV show?
拜託，我主演的影集耶？
-I don't know if I'm good enough. -I am.
我都不知道我配不配 我配
What are you talking about? You're a terrific actor.
喬伊，你在說什麼？ 你是個很棒的演員
-You really think so? -How can you even ask that question?
真的嗎？ 你怎麼能這麼問
-She's pretty. -Yeah. And she's really nice too.
她真漂亮 對，人也很好
She taught me all about how to work with cameras...
她教我怎麼面對鏡頭
and "smell the fart" acting.
和聞屁演技法
-I'm sorry. What? -Excuse me?
什麼？
It's like you got so many lines to learn so fast...
因為在短時間內要背很多台詞
sometimes you need time to remember your next one.
有時得停下來想下一句
So while you're thinking of it, you take this pause where you look intense.
在你想的時候 要來個大停頓，表情故作嚴肅
You know, like this:
就像這樣
Okay.
好
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
該我了該我了
Mrs. Wallace? I'm Dr. Drake Ramorey, your sister's surgeon.
華勒斯太太，我是拉莫瑞醫生 令妹的神經外科醫生
You sister is suffering from a...
令妹得了一種…
Well,Eva,we've done some excellent work here.
伊娃，偶們有不湊的進展 （我們有不錯的進展）
And I would have to say your problem is quite clear.
老俗唆，你的困老很清此 （老實說，你的困擾很清楚）
All you want is a tinkle
你只是想要一個老二
What you envy's a schwang
你在忌妒男人
A thing through which you can tinkle
你想要拿它來撒尿
Or play with or simply let hang
或是把玩，或是掛在那邊
I play Al Pacino's butt.
我演艾爾帕西諾的屁股
All right?
好嗎？
He goes into the shower and then, I'm his butt.
他進去淋浴 然後我就是他的屁股
-Oh,my God. -Come on,you guys.
-天哪 -別這樣
This is a movie and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!
這是一部電影 艾爾帕西諾主演，很不得了
It's terrific. You deserve this. After years of struggling...
的確很棒 你當之無愧，努力了這麼久
you've finally cracked your way into show business.
終於可以「屁美」別人了
Okay,fine, make jokes. I don't care. This is a big break for me.
好，你們笑吧，我不在乎 這是我的一大突破
-No,you're right,it is. -Yeah.
你說得很對
So,you gonna invite us to the big opening?
你會找我們去看你 「精屁」的演出嗎？
All right,I'm out of here. Wish me luck.
好，我要走了，祝我好運
Good luck,good luck We all wish you good luck
加油，加油，我們祝你好運
Yeah,whatever.
隨便啦
Wow,if I could dance, I'd be a triple threat.
要是我會跳舞就更可怕了
It's your turn.
該你了
Oh,are we playing this?
我們有在玩喔？
How'd the audition go?
試鏡結果如何？
Terrible. I messed up every word. I shouldn't even be an actor.
很爛 我把台詞都念壞了 我不該當演員的
Wait. Are you pretending it didn't go well, but it really did go well?
等等，你又在假裝不順利了嗎
-Yeah, did I fool you? -Totally!
-對，有唬過你們嗎？ -一愣一愣的
-So it did go well? -Amazingly well!
所以很順利羅 順利得不得了
-Great! -It's down to me and two other guys.
太好了 只剩我和另外兩個人三選一 天哪
And they're really good.
那兩個人都很厲害
One's from those allergy commercials who's chased by flowers.
其中一個就是在過敏廣告裡 被巨無霸花朵追來追去的人
Oh,I love that guy!
我好喜歡那個人
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
What am I doing?
我在幹什麼？
I'm so nervous,you know? The callback is tomorrow at 5:00.
我好緊張 明天下午5點才要複試
-I feel like my head's gonna explode. -Well,it is overdue.
我的頭好像要爆炸了 你的頭早該爆了
-Don't worry. You'll be fine. -But it's so much pressure.
放心，你一定沒問題 壓力真的好大
What you guys do is different. I don't know if you'd understand.
很抱歉，但你們的工作很不同 我不知道你們能不能體會
Yeah,we don't have pressure at our jobs.
是啊，我們的工作都沒有壓力
I know what time it is,but I'm looking at the wee-ness and I'm not happy.
我知道現在幾點了 但是我對這份報告很不滿意
Well,I'm tearing the lettuce.
我在撕生菜
-Is it dirty? -Don't worry,I'll wash it.
它髒嗎？ 放心，我會洗
Don't. I like it dirty.
不必，我喜歡髒的
That's your call.
你決定就好
So what are you going to do next?
你接下來要做什麼？
I thought I'd cut up the tomatoes.
我要切蕃茄
Are they firm?
它們結實嗎？
-They're all right. -You sure they haven't gone bad?
還不差 你確定它們沒有變壞？
You sure they're not very,very bad?
你確定它們不是很壞很壞？
-No,really. They're okay. -You gonna slice them real nice?
它們還好 你會把它們切得很漂亮嗎？
Actually,I was gonna do them julienne.
其實我想切絲
I'm out of here.
我要走了
I'm quitting. I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong...
摩妮卡，我要辭職 我幫一個老女人擠進丁字褲
and she didn't even buy it.
結果她也沒買
I'm quitting. That's it. I'm talking to my boss right now.
我要辭職 我現在就要跟老闆說
Yes,I am. Yes,I am.
我要我要我要…
Bye. Call me when you get this message.
再見，聽到留言請回電
Well,what happened?
怎麼了？
Well, he came in for a massage, and everything was fine until...
他來按摩，本來都沒事 後來…
Oh,my God.
天哪
And all of a sudden, his hands weren't the problem anymore.
然後突然間毛手毛腳成了小事
-Was it? -Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
他有沒有… 用來搭帳棚都綽綽有餘
You ate my sandwich?
你吃了我的三明治？
It was a mistake. It could happen to anyone.
很單純的錯誤，誰都可能會犯
Really?
是嗎？
Now calm down.
你別激動
Come look in my office. Some of it may still be in the trash.
來我的辦公室找 垃圾桶裡可能還有
-What? -Well,it was quite large.
什麼？ 它很大
I had to throw most of it away.
我只好扔掉一大半
You threw my sandwich away?
你…你扔掉我的三明治
My sandwich?
我的三明治
My sandwich!
It's just,I want this part so much.
我好想拿到這個角色
If I don't get this part, I'm never gonna eat macaroni and cheese again.
要是我沒拿到 我就再也不吃起司通心面
I didn't say that. That doesn't count.
不，我沒說，我騙人
Come on,guys. It's not like I moved to Europe.
別這樣，我又不是搬去歐洲
I just moved across the hall.
我只是搬到對面
And we would have you over all the time...
我們也想經常請你們來坐
if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
但是摩妮卡會過敏
You're right,I could never lie to you.
沒錯，我騙不了你們
She hates you.
她討厭你們
Should I get that?
要接嗎？
Hello? No,Joey's not here right now. Can I take a message?
你好 喬伊現在不在，你要留言嗎？
Yeah,okay. So the audition's been moved from 5:00 to 2:30?
好，試鏡從5點改到2點半？
Okay,great. Bye.
好的，再見
-Aren't you dressed yet? -Am I naked again?
你還沒穿衣服？ 我又光著身體了？
We're meeting my parents in 15 minutes.
我們15分鐘後要去見我爸媽
I was just talking to the guys. Look at them.
好，我只是在跟它們聊天
Is it okay if they come visit?
你看它們嘛 它們可以去找我們嗎？
What about my allergies?
那我的過敏怎麼辦？
Right. Your allergies.
也對，你會過敏
All her. She hates you.
都是她，她討厭你們
Yes! All right.
漂亮
How cool would it be if you could watch a life-size version of this?
要是這些小人能變成真人大小 該有多酷？
-I mean,how crazy would that be? -As crazy as soccer?
該有多過癮？ 跟足球一樣過癮？
Hello?
你好
What are you talking about? The audition's at 5.
你在說什麼？5點才試鏡
Well,nobody told me.
沒有人告訴我
Who'd you talk to?
你跟誰說的？
Never mind.
沒事
You mean you didn't get it from this?
這樣你看不懂嗎？
-The allergy guy got the part. Thanks. -Maybe we can fix it.
-那個過敏人入選了，謝謝你啊 -也許還可以補救
Maybe we can send him some big flowers and scare him!
我們可以送巨無霸花去嚇他
How could you do this? This could've turned my career around.
你怎麼能這樣？ 這個角色可以讓我的事業翻紅
I messed up,okay? I'm sorry. I really messed up.
是我不好 對不起，我真的錯了
Why'd you answer my phone?
你根本也不住這裡了 幹嘛接我的電話？
-I have a machine! -Which I bought for you.
-我有答錄機 -是我買給你的
Taught you how to use it. You thought it was a copier.
還教你怎麼使用 你以為它是影印機
If there was anything I could do, I'd do it.
我願意盡全力挽救這個錯誤
Everybody's allowed one mistake,right?
但是人起碼可以犯一次錯
He could have gotten me a VCR or golf clubs.
他可以送我錄影機 可以送我高爾夫球具
But no,he has to get me the "Woman Repeller."
可是他偏偏要讓我把女人嚇跑
The eyesore from the "Liberace House of Crap!"
一個廢五金行裡最醜的東西
-It's not that bad. -Easy for you to say.
沒那麼嚴重
You don't have to sport a reject from the "Mr. T" collection.
你又不必戴著 被某個老粗淘汰的金飾到處跑
I pity the fool who puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!
「我真同情戴這個手飾的人」 「真的」
I pity the fool that...
「我真同情戴這個…」 你好
When you were late last night, Kathy and I were talking and...
你昨天晚歸 凱西和我聊了起來
one thing led to another and....
事情演變到後來就…
And what? Did you sleep with her?
就什麼？你跟她上床？
-No! No,I just kissed her. -What? That's even worse!
沒有，我只是吻了她 什麼？那樣更糟！
-How? -I don't know! But it's the same!
怎麼會更糟？ 我不知道，反正都一樣
I have no excuses. I was over the line.
你說得對，我無話可說 我太過分了
Over the line?
過分？
You're so far past the line you can't even see it!
你根本就過分到...
The line is a dot to you!
連過分見到你都會說你過分
I'm not saying you should magically forgive me.
我不是要你奇跡式的原諒我
But you're not perfect. You've made errors in judgment.
但你也不完美 你也做過錯誤的判斷
Name one!
舉個例子
What happened?
怎麼回事？
Man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!
他答應不拿沙發椅的
How were you locked in? And where the hell's all of our stuff?
怎麼回事？你怎麼會被關進去 我們的東西呢？
This guy came to look at the unit...
有一個人來看櫃子
and he didn't think it was big enough to fit a man.
他說它塞不下一個大人
So you got in voluntarily?
所以你就自願進去？
I was trying to make a sale!
我想把櫃子賣出去
If I ever run into him again, know what I'll do?
要是讓我碰上他 你猜我會怎樣？
Bend over?
把屁股翹起來？
There's Lori.
她來了
Remember,no trading. You get the pretty one,I get the mess.
記住，不准交換 美女是你的，失戀女是我的
-Hi,Joey. -Hey.
喬伊
Well,well. Look what you brought.
他就是你帶來的人
And what did you bring?
你又帶了誰來？
She's checking her coat.
她在寄放外套
Joey,I'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands.
喬伊，我要去洗個手
Will you get me a white Zinfandel and a glass of red for Janice.
你幫我叫一杯白酒 幫珍妮絲叫一杯紅酒
Janice?
珍妮絲？珍妮絲？
Oh,my God!
我…的…天哪
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
喬伊的裁縫吃我豆腐
What?
什麼？
No way. I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
不可能 我找他做了12年衣服
You said he'd do my inseam...
拜託啦，他說要量褲管內側
then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was...
然後他的手一路摸上來 然後就…
What?
怎樣？
Cupping.
包住了
That's how they do pants!
褲子就是那樣量的
-Isn't that how a tailor measures? -Yes,yes,it is. In prison!
羅斯，你告訴他 褲子不都是那樣量的？ 是啊是啊…在監獄裡
I said name one!
叫你舉一個就好
-I can't believe I did this. -Stop beating yourself up.
我居然這麼粗心，我真白癡 別再自責了
People make mistakes. These things happen.
人都會犯錯，這是難免的
There aren't any messages you've forgotten to give me?
你沒有忘記幫我記留言吧？
Apparently,you're not very good at it.
是你自己遜
-Do you think he'll forgive me? -Of course.
你們覺得他會原諒我嗎？ 當然會
The important thing is that you forgive yourself.
但最重要的是 你得原諒自己
-You know what,I kind of have. -Already?
其實我已經原諒自己了 這麼快？
That was pretty bad what you did.
你犯的錯蠻嚴重的
He will forgive you.
他會原諒你的
I like to bring a pad with me when I answer the phone, okay?
我接電話時都會帶便條紙… 好啦
-You didn't see how mad he was. -I'm sure he'll forgive you.
你沒看到他氣成什麼樣子  他一定會原諒你的
We've all been there. You fight, you make up. That's how it works.
我們都有這種經驗 吵架，和解，就是這樣
It took two people to break up this relationship!
這段感情會破裂是兩個人的錯
Yeah! You and that copy girl...
對，你和影印店那個女的
which yesterday you took responsibility for!
你昨天表明願意負責
I didn't know what I was taking responsibility for.
我不知道我負的是什麼責
-I didn't finish the letter. -What?
我沒把信看完 什麼？
-I fell asleep. -You fell asleep?
我睡著了 你睡著了？
It was 5:30 in the morning.
當時是早上5點半
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
你一廢話就廢話了十八頁
Front and back!
正反面都寫滿了
And by the way?  Y-O-U, apostrophe R-E means,"you are."
還有 「你得」是指「你必須」
Y-O-U-R means "your."
「你的」是代表所有格
I can't believe I thought of getting back together with you.
我居然會想跟你復合
We are so over!
我們根本就完了
Fine by me!
無所謂
And just so you know, it's not that common...
順便告訴你 那種事並不常見
it doesn't happen to every guy, and it is a big deal!
並非男人都會那樣 那是很嚴重的
I knew it!
我就知道
-You had no right to go out with him. -That's ridiculous..
你沒有權利和他約會 這真是太荒謬…
-You sold me out! -I did not!
你出賣我 我沒有出賣你
-You did! You sold me.. -Would you let me talk?
-你有！你出賣我...  -讓我說話好嗎？
Did you just flick me?
你彈我的額頭嗎？
Well,you wouldn't let me finish and..
你不讓我說完，我很…
Stop it!
-Stop. -Stop.
-All right. No,let's not do this. -No!
-好，不要這樣  -不
-Happy thoughts. -No!
-想想快樂的事 -不
-快樂的事  -不！
Okay,now I'm gonna kick some ass!
好，我要發威了
All right. Now,I will let go if you both stop.
你們住手，我就放手
-Fine. -Fine.
好吧
There we go.
這不就結了
You know what? If we were in prison, you guys would be my bitches.
如果我們在坐牢 你們就是我的嘍囉
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
兄弟，如何啊
You hide my clothes? I'm wearing everything you own.
你藏我的衣服 我就穿你全部的衣服
Oh,my God!
我的天哪
Look at me,I'm Chandler! Could I be wearing any more clothes?
看啊，我是錢德 我穿的衣服夠多吧？
Maybe if I wasn't going commando.
因為我去玩野戰遊戲
I tell you,it's hot with all this on. I'd better not do any lunges.
穿這麼多衣服真熱 我最好別做弓箭步
Joey?
喬伊？
Got you the Joey special! Two pizzas!
我買了歡樂套餐，有兩個披薩
喬伊？
Hello? Damn it!
你好 又來了
Hello?
你好
No,Joey's not here right now, but I can take a message. I think.
喬伊現在不在 我可以幫你留言…應該吧
He's still got a chance for the part? That's great news!
他還有機會？真是太好了
Well,no,obviously not for the actor who was mauled by his dog.
我不是說那位被狗咬傷的演員
That's great. I'll give Joey the message.
太好了，我會轉告喬伊，謝謝
Yes!
漂亮
Okay.
好
Mac...
麥克…
audition...
試鏡…
at 2:00.
2點鐘
Allergy...
過敏…
actor...
演員…
attacked.
遭攻擊
By dog...
被狗…
not...
不是…
flowers.
被花
-Tell me you got the message. -What message?
-請告訴我你有收到留言 -什麼留言？
The actor playing Mac couldn't do it. They needed you at 2.
要演麥克的演員不能演 他們要你2點過去
What? It's 6:00!
什麼？明明是6點
Look! I wrote it on the board!
我有寫在留言板上
I wrote it down, then went looking for you!
我寫在留言板上 然後跑遍整個紐約找你
I went to Ross's, the coffee house...
我跑去羅斯家，跑去咖啡館
I went to any place they make sandwiches!
跑去每一個有三明治的地方
-I can't believe this,Chandler! -I'm sorry.
怎麼這樣啦 對不起
-I don't know what to say! -You might say congratulations!
-我不知道該說什麼  -那就說恭喜吧
I saw the board, I went to the audition, I got the part!
我看到留言板，跑去試鏡 我中了
Was that funny? I was worried.
你覺得很好笑嗎？ 我剛才真的很擔心
-I'm sorry. -That fake-out thing is just mean.
有時候這樣騙人真的很惡劣
Oh,I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
抱歉，我不是故意要害你內疚
Well,that's good.
那就好
Because you didn't! And I'm incredibly happy for you!
因為我沒有內疚 我好替你高興
That's mean!
你好惡劣
-You had me going! -We could do this all day.
你害我慚愧 再玩就玩不完了
Yeah,you're right.
也對
Let's talk about what a huge star I'm gonna be.
好，我們來聊聊我會有多紅
You're gonna be huge! I'm gonna hug you!
你會變成超級大明星
-You hug me! -All right.
我要抱你 來抱吧
-Do we do this too much? -I think so.
我們會不會太愛抱了？ 我也覺得
-Yeah. Get off me. -Yeah.
放開我 就是啊
"C.H.E.E.S.E., I'm not leaving without you.
吉事，我不會扔下你的
Route your backup power source through your CPU."
你從中央處理器 啟動備用電源
"l can't! My circuits are fried! They're fried, I tell you!"
沒辦法，我的電路燒焦了 焦到不能再焦
"Then I'll carry you!"
那我就背你
"That'll be a neat trick..."
好棒的招數啊
"when you're dead!"
等你死了再說
You don't have to yell.
羅斯，你不必用喊的
There was just an explosion. My hearing would be impaired.
剛才有爆炸，我的聽力會受損
I thought you were great.
我覺得你很棒
For a minute,I was like, "Where'd Ross go?"
剛才我甚至覺得「羅斯呢？」
Thank you. And that first scene where you meet Mac...
謝謝 你和麥克見面的第一場戲…
-Yeah? -Oh,my God. I mean...
怎樣？ 我的天哪
And you know what?
That's enough for today. Thanks for your help.
今天就到此為止，多謝幫忙
-Holding us back. -Totally.
他欺壓新人 就是啊